(Penny:)Oh, God. I think
I see where this is going.
(Howard:)Her name was
Glissinda the Troll.
(Howard:)Bernadette walked in on me
(Howard:)while we were doing
the cyber-nasty
(Howard:)under the Bridge of Souls.
(Penny:)Oh, you're right.
(Penny:)That is so embarrassing.
(Howard:)Would you talk to her?
(Penny:)Bernadette or the troll?
(Howard:)Bernadette. She
was so mad at me,
(Howard:)she wouldn't even listen
to my side of the story.
(Penny:)Well, what was your side?
(Howard:)Well, for all we know,
(Howard:)Glissinda the Troll
wasn't even a real woman.
(Howard:)I mean, she could've been
a 50-year-old truck driver
(Howard:)in New Jersey.
(Penny:)Really? And that didn't
make her feel better?
(Howard:)Will you talk to her, see
if there's any chance at all
(Howard:)we could get back together?
(Penny:)Oh, gee, Howard,
I really don't want
(Penny:)to get in the middle of this.
(Howard:)No. Why would you?
(Howard:)I'm just another lonely
nerd, living with his mother,
(Howard:)trying to find any scrap
of happiness he can.
(Howard:)You know, maybe to make up
for the fact that his dad